bnonews.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy - BNO News

Last update: June 29, 2015

At BNO News B.V., your privacy is important to us. This page will help you understand what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit bnonews.com. We never sell your personal information to third parties. However, our website collects statistical data and uses cookies from the following services:

\- Google Analytics  
\- Google AdSense

As most other websites do, BNO News collects and uses the data contained in log files. The information in these logs include your internet protocol (IP) address, your internet service provider, the browser you used to visit our website, the time you visited our website, and which pages you visited on our site. This information is statistical data that is used for system administration and performance reports.

This website uses cookies from Google services, including Google Analytics and Google AdSense. Google Analytics is a web analytics tool that helps website owners understand how visitors engage with their website. This allows us to view a variety of reports about how visitors interact with their website so that they can improve it. 

Like many services, Google Analytics uses first-party cookies to track visitor interactions. Cookies contain information that is transferred to your computer’s hard drive. These cookies are used to store information, such as the time that the current visit occurred, whether the visitor has been to the site before and what site referred the visitor to the web page. 

Google Analytics collects information anonymously. It reports website trends without identifying individual visitors. You can opt out of Google Analytics without affecting how you visit our site – for more information on opting out of being tracked by Google Analytics across all websites you use, visit [this Google page](https://tools.google.com/%3Cbr%20/%3Edlpage/gaoptout).

BNO News also uses third party advertisements to help support our business. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our website, which will also send these these third party advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) certain information, including your IP address, your ISP, the browser you used to visit our site, and, in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geo-targeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see:   
http://www.networkadvertising.org/  
managing/opt_out.asp

We also may use DART cookies for ad serving through Google’s DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements). This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests (”interest based targeting”).

The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history (For example, if you have been viewing sites about visiting Las Vegas, you may see Las Vegas hotel advertisements when viewing a non-related site, such as on a site about hockey). DART uses “non personally identifiable information”. It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers.

You can opt-out of this ad serving on all sites using this advertising by visiting [this](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx) site. 

You can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

Deleting cookies does not mean you are permanently opted out of any advertising program. Unless you have settings that disallow cookies, the next time you visit a site running the advertisements, a new cookie will be added.

If you have any questions regarding our privacy policy and use of cookies, please contact legal@bnonews.com
